<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
<addon id="plugin.program.flixwizard" name="[COLOR limegreen]Flix[/COLOR]Wizard" version="2.0.6.1" provider-name="k0diuser234">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" />
        <import addon="script.module.six" />
        <import addon="script.kodi.android.update" optional="true" version="1.1.7" />
        <import addon="script.speedtester" optional="true" version="1.1.2" />
    </requires>

    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>

    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="startup.py" start="startup" />

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">[COLOR limegreen]Flix[/COLOR]Wizard</summary>
        <description lang="en">[COLOR limegreen]Flix[/COLOR]Wizard offers many maintenance features, selective add-on data saving, and automated build installs. It is also the home of the KodiFlix Build and hopefully more to come. Push Pull Test 5</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <source>https://www.github.com/unkn0wn234/plugin.program.flixwizard/</source>
        <news>
2.0.7
 - Fix Error when using default log settings
2.0.6
 - Fix regex for formatting tags
 - Fix theme selection after build install
 - Fix downloading into invalid path
2.0.5
 - Add Enable All Add-ons after Build Install
2.0.4
 - Fix leftover broken dialogs
2.0.3
 - Don't show previous version builds in Matrix
2.0.2
 - Replace remaining occurences of LOGNOTICE
2.0.1
 - Add attribution to @slamious
2.0.0
 - Initial Matrix support
1.4.5
 - Fix bugs with unintended files being cleared`
1.4.4
 - Transfer ownership
1.4.3
 - Fix missing artwork on items (thanks @xulek)
1.4.2
 - A few bug fixes
1.4.1
 - Fix crash on fresh installs
1.4.0
 - Fix APK Installer
 - Convert official APK downloader to use official script
 - Add scrollbar to Save Data dialog
 - Fix skin path in build info
1.3.7
 - Fix import lock error
1.3.6
 - Fix notifications
 - Cleanup log files
1.3.5
 - Add Fen
 - Add Shadow
 - Fix restoring saved data every boot
1.3.4
 - Fix bad indent
1.3.3
 - Fix Unicode characters in notification window
1.3.2
 - Fix build restore
1.3.1
 - Fix "Keep Login Info" menu
1.3.0
 - Fix formatting of saved restore times
 - Fix local build zip being deleted on restore
 - Add YouTube API saving
 - Remove broken context menus
 - Fix repeating dialogs from shortcuts/favorites
 - Remove "Normal Install" option
 - Add "Logging Tools" menu
 - Add option to save guisettings.xml
 - Add TMDbHelper Fanart.tv saving
 - More fixes for OS X
 - Fix Seren Fanart.tv saving
1.2.9
 - Fix NuMb3r5 cache clearing
 - Fix hang during repo force check
 - Fix logins being restored every startup
 - Fix some file permission errors
 - Fix OS X backup errors
1.2.8
 - Add Gaia PM OAuth
 - Fix binary add-on restoration
 - Fix some issues with old settings
 - Fix timing on many startup tasks
1.2.7
 - Add TheMovieDb Helper
1.2.6
 - Fix Seren PM OAuth
1.2.5
 - Fix typo in debridit.py
1.2.4
 - Cover more edge cases during binary detection
1.2.3
 - Fix notification ID bug
1.2.2
 - Add Seren PM OAuth
 - Add AllDebrid spport for Gaia, Seren, ResolveURL, and URLResolver
1.2.1
 - General bug fixes
1.2.0
 - Silence save data notifications on startup
 - Fix Addon Installer menu
 - Convert addons.txt to JSON format
1.1.1
 - Fix error on advancedsettings categories
1.1.0
 - Add back advancedsettings area under System Tweaks/Fixes
 - Rudimentary version of advancedsettings editor. Can currently only handle editing pre-existing tags under 'cache' and 'network'.
 - Convert advanced.txt to JSON format
 - Add "built-in" advancedsettings.xml presets
1.0.3
 - Update artwork
 - Fix rare issues with URLs not working
 - Fix repetitive build prompt (again)
 - Fix builds downloading twice
 - Fix title coloring on notifications
 - Fix auto repo install
 - Fix first run settings not being respected
1.0.2
 - Fix crash in login menu
 - Fix auto install repo
1.0.1
 - Fix double startup
 - Fix repetitive build prompt
 - Fix main menu not opening on Krypton
 - Fix notification timeout
 - Fix crash in Trakt menu
1.0.0
 - Initial Commit
        </news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.png</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.seren" version="2.0.19" name="Seren" provider-name="Nixgates">
    <requires>
        <import addon="script.module.future" version="0.17.1"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" version="6.8.3"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.6.2"/>
        <import addon="context.seren" version="2.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.inputstreamhelper" version="0.3.3"/>
        <import addon="script.module.myconnpy" version="1.1.7"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="seren.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <reuselanguageinvoker>false</reuselanguageinvoker>
        <summary lang="en">Seren - Modular Multi-source Addon</summary>
        <description lang="en">Seren is a modular provider based, cloud service streaming software that is tightly
            interwoven with Trakt. Seren provides the freedom to view media from a single menu system from service
            providers of the users choosing. Please Note: This addon requires the use of a compatible cloud service.
        </description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 3, 29 June 2007</license>
        <forum/>
        <website>https://github.com/nixgates/plugin.video.seren</website>
        <source>https://github.com/nixgates/plugin.video.seren</source>
        <disclaimer lang="en">
            Last updated: September 09, 2019.
            The information contained within the Seren software (the "Service") is for general information purposes
            only.
            The author assumes no responsibility for errors, omissions in the contents on the Service, nor does it
            assume responsibility for any material provided by any external services.
            The use of the Service does not author the user to engage in any kind of illegal, criminal or tortious
            activity through the use of the software, including infringement of any third party intellectual property
            rights (including without limitation copyright, trade marks, patent, trade secrets and confidential
            information), fraud, child pornography, trafficking in obscene material, violation of applicable export
            restrictions, drug dealing, gambling, harassment, stalking, spamming, hacking, sending of viruses or other
            harmful files or illegal posting of computer passwords or computer code.
            The user is responsible for all their activity in connection with the use of the Service and the author
            reserves the right to report any potentially criminal activity to appropriate law enforcement agencies.
            The user must not transmit to or via the Service, any material that may infringe the intellectual property
            rights of any third party, or any defamatory, derogatory or offensive material or publication.
            In no event shall the author of this software be liable for any special, direct, indirect, consequential, or
            incidental damages or any damages whatsoever, whether in an action of contract, negligence or other tort,
            arising out of or in connection with the use of the Service or the contents of the Service.
            The author reserves the right to make additions, deletions, or modification to the contents on the Service
            at any time without prior notice.
            The author of this software does not warrant that the software is free of viruses or other harmful
            components.
            Seren may contain links to external websites that are not provided or maintained by or in any way affiliated
            with the author.
            Please note that the author does not guarantee the accuracy, relevance, timeliness, or completeness of any
            information on these external websites.
        </disclaimer>
        <assets>
            <icon>ico-seren-2.jpg</icon>
            <fanart>fanart-seren-2.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
        <news>
            Changelog 2.0.19
            Fix handling of unicode in URLs, TV Networks and Searching issues on Leia
            Fix TV show years
            Fix PM CacheAssist status updates
            Only try to auto-cache if auto-cache is actually enabled
            Change default threadpool size and provide user settings
            Increase timeout configuration setting maximum permitted value
            Make pre-scrape respect new maximum value for timeout
            Change approach for deaccenting clean_title and transliterate actor names
            During prescrape, don't pop up the too restrictive filters window and just use unfiltered list for sorting
            Fix Kodi Bookmark Clearing with MySQL DB support
            Temporarily disable totaltime progress indicators as they break our resume on Matrix
            Fix TVDB session issues
            Fix XBOX Database Issues
            Fix database pickling issues
            Fix Kodi crashes in Leia
            Fix Kodi crashes in Matrix (with exception of reuselanguageinvoker enabled when stopping playback combined with widgets)
            Change default value of reuselanguageinvoker to False and force use addon provided value on upgrade
            Ensure we release all Kodi objects to prevent memory leaks and crashes
            Ensure we close all requests sessions to prevent memory leaks
            Workaround occasional python bug with strptime in lambda functions
            Made Kodi version detection algorithm more resilient and cover pre-release versions
            Logging enhancements
            Added Arabic translations

            Changelog 2.0.18
            Fix the thread pool issues
            Added logic to push down the country_origin to be used by the scrapers
            Original title swap now only occurs for display, use unicode everywhere
            Fixed normalization function retuning unnormalized values
            Fix for genre multi-select always showing same items
            Fixed local TZ conversion for dates in Upcoming, Source Select and OSD
            Real Debrid use status_codes to determine what are good requests
            Make sure we have all parts for the calculation of the bookmarks
            Added regex to parse semver out of version label
            Re-implemented update checker that will work regardless of repo changes

            Changelog 2.0.17:
            Fix for shows search and TVDB empty data
            Fix handling of timestamp creation to be UTC compliant
            Fix timezone code taking unix path on Windows
            Added a fall through for android getprop timezone detection
            Handle invalid dates from metadata indexer when obtaining year value.
            Fix Matrix UI spins on closing download manager
            Add check for invalid list position in download manager returned by an empty list
            Fix isFolder bool for download manager
            Fix resume progress indicators
            Calculate resumetime at bookmark insert for movies
            Add support for clearing bookmarks on Matrix
            Fix view_type has no attribute isdigit bug
            Ensure studio info value in seasons/episodes
            Add provider package version information to existing logging item
            Handle removal of legacy provider meta file both on uninstall and upgrade
            Replaced seekTime with execute of BigSkipForward
            Fix Simplejson decode error not caught bug
            Handle exception instances from a4ksubtitles
            Fix pagination for genre multi-select
            Fix paging of Finish Watching has same items bug
            Fixed show pack suffixes and checking of 1x1 episode naming
            Updated missing codes and added it-IT, fr-FR and ar-SA translations
            Update Danish language strings

            Changelog 2.0.16:
            Fix addon update check
            Fix trakt module attempting to refresh when not authorised

            Changelog 2.0.15:
            Fixed python depend

            Changelog 2.0.14:
            Fixed scraping issue if title is not present at IMDB
            Added workarounds for syncing trakt database on xbox
            Fixed Trending/Popular Trakt lists repeating
            Seperated sort and pagination setting for Trakt collection
            Applied sort and pagination settings for collection to unfinished shows in collection
            Re-worked date handling to use UTC for all internal uses and convert to local on display
            Fixed pagination on recently watched shows menu
            Fixed source sorting issue for py3
            Fixed race condition in pre-term for py3
            File size now displayed on resolver dialog
            Updated some dutch translations
            Fixed hosters not being handled correctly at scrape
            Fix reuselanguageinvoker default
            Fixed background sync attempting to run when no Trakt auth present

            Changelog 2.0.13
            Fixed settings not sticking when using reuselanguageinvoker
            Fixed reuselanguageinvoke status not sticking after toggling
            Reuselangugageinvoker state now forced on startup
            Reduced Trakt retries on server failures
            Increased backoff timeout for retries
            Fixed playback for special episodes failing
            Eased timeout issues for bookmarks
            Fixed non-direct, non-debrid hosters appearing in source select
            Fix spanish translation file name
            Fixed title sorting for lists with articles
            Fixed paging on new shows

            Changelog 2.0.12
            Fix for source select, tested on 4 skins

            Changelog 2.0.11
            Take preventative measures to reduce overloading Trakt servers
            Increase local show/season statistic refreshing
            Fixed cloud source sorting
            Fixed HEVC source sorting
            New shows api call now pulls english and local language from Trakt
            Modified database commit method to allow for xbox support
            Reformat source select screen again to allow better filename displaying
            Fixed next button showing on next up menu
            Removed pycryptodome dependency, this will need to be requested on a per provider basis
            Fixed pre-term
            Fixed empty search results raising exception
            Fixed auto episode resuming
            Fixed superficial exceptions in play dialogs
            Updated danish language strings

            Changelog 2.0.10
            Fixed issue with milling seasons to often
            Added checks when attempting to cache magnet
            Fixed tvshows new
            Fetching of RD account details after auth fixed
            Fixed spanish translation folder name
            Reformat of source select to allow larger file name sizes
            Fixed race condition in ThreadPool
            Added fallback for text color if skin color could not be inherited
            Add legacy param support for smart play playlist creation
            Fix hide the hiding of unaired episodes from non mixed episode lists
            Removed default action setting until a appropriate workaround for kodi setting is achieved
            Wrapped player interactions with Trakt API with Try/Excepts to allow network failures
            Added fallback method if no thumb art is available
            Added temporary workaround for ratings issue in add_directory_items
            Fixed keep-alive in player module. (Fixes dialogs, playlist creation, marking as watched if not caused by network failure)
            Allowed exceptions in cache check to allow for debrid providers who are offline
            Replaced ok dialogs for connection issues with notifications


            Changelog 2.0.9:
            Fixed RD cloud scraping
            Fixed issue if all providers were disabled scraping would run as if all were enabled
            Fixed smartplay and legacy paramas support
            Fixed bug causing failure when checking art from TMDB
            Fixed user lists menus
            Added spanish translation
            Fixed backing out from menu when opened from widget (having to backout multiple times)
            Fixed season watch markers
            Fixed hidden_items handling with New Shows menu

            Changelog 2.0.8:
            Temporary Workaround for trakt items not providing trakt_id
            Better RD episode resolving
            Better episode identification during resolving
            Catch WindowsError exception when handling skins
            Fix text highlight selection
            Cool down background service on failure

            Changelog 2.0.7:
            Fixed All debrid torrent resolving
            Fixed movie resuming
            Fixed issue with limited providers running at scrape
            Fixed AD re-auth
            Changes to attempt to fix XBOX support and ascii issues with timezones
            Fixed unaired episodes showing blank
            Fixed AD User info fetching
            Fixed ghost providers
            Fixed TypeError with pre-termination

            Changelog 2.0.6:
            Create Skins directory if missing
            Allow failure in pre-term until investigated

            Changelog 2.0.5:
            Allow more failures that will require to be investigated further in the future

            Changelog 2.0.4:
            Safe get release title when cloud scraping
            Allow and log failures in maintenance process

            Changelog 2.0.3:
            Added default value of None for skin color when attempting to pull color from user's skin

            Changelog 2.0.2:
            Force table re-fresh is sync database fails to rebuild when updating

            Changelog 2.0.1:
            Fix last_meta_update value to reflect new Seren version

            Changleog 2.0.0:

            Added Download Manager
            Complete re-write of Trakt Sync Database
            Metadata handler introduced and complete re-write of handling of metadata
            Settings that modify metadata can now be changed on the fly and do not require a rebuild
            Users can now manually resolve a file from the source select screen
            Users can now manually cache a specific source from the source select screen
            Complete re-write of menu handling
            Introduced globals module to handle global variables for interpreter
            Implement re-use language invoker setting from Kodi
            Pre-emptive termination now disabled for background Pre-scrapes and timeout set to max for background scrapes
            New artwork and custom dialogs
            Metadata now upadted on the fly when updated item encountered from Trakt
            Next Up menu now populated from local database
            Sync has been fleshed out to include even more meta data during cycle
            Failures to auto resolve now prompt user in case they wish to manually interrupt
            Items are now able to supply multiple images for any given type for skins that make use of it
            Support for Python 3
            Global thread lock now implemented for required methods (prevents multiple syncs occuring at once and other locks)
            InputStreamAdaptive support
            Providers now have the abiity to implement settings
            Provider packages can now elect to make use of their own background services
            Provider packages can now offer images for each provider
            Cache and Sync database items are now pickled
            Complete re-write of resovler module and consolidated code
            Kodi 19 support
            All Debrid implementation now fully featured
            Sources can now be sorted by filesize low to high for users that wish to do so
            Forcing widget refresh after playback now optional
            Zip manager implemented for handling of zip files
            Skin Manager rework
            Automated resolving now more reliable
            OMDB API implemented
            Feedback provided at scrape if no providers are found
            Feedback provided at scrape if no debrid providers are setup
            Debrid account status now visible from Seren settings
        </news>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.flixwizard" name="[COLOR limegreen][B]Flix[/B][/COLOR]Wizard Repository" version="0.9.1" provider-name="k0diuser234">
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="[COLOR limegreen][B]Flix[/B][/COLOR]Wizard Repository">
        <dir minversion="18.0" maxversion="18.9.0">
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/unkn0wn234/repository.flixwizard/master/leia/zips/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/unkn0wn234/repository.flixwizard/master/leia/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/unkn0wn234/repository.flixwizard/master/leia/zips/</datadir>
        </dir>
        <dir minversion="18.9.0">
            <info compressed="false">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/unkn0wn234/repository.flixwizard/master/matrix/zips/addons.xml</info>
            <checksum>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/unkn0wn234/repository.flixwizard/master/matrix/zips/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
            <datadir zip="true">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/unkn0wn234/repository.flixwizard/master/matrix/zips/</datadir>
        </dir>
    </extension>

    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>[COLOR limegreen][B]Flix[/B][/COLOR]Wizard</summary>
        <description>The official home of [COLOR limegreen][B]Flix[/B][/COLOR]Wizard.</description>
        <disclaimer></disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <source>https://www.github.com/unkn0wn234/repository.flixwizard/</source>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="skin.arctic.horizonmod" name="Arctic Horizon MOD" provider-name="jurialmunkey, unkn0wn234" version="0.5.66">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.15.0" />
        <import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="0.4.0" />
        <import addon="script.skinvariables" version="0.2.3" />
        <import addon="script.image.resource.select" version="0.0.5" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.themoviedb.helper" version="4.2.3" />
        <import addon="plugin.program.autocompletion" version="1.0.1" />
        <import addon="resource.images.studios.white" version="0.0.10" />
        <import addon="resource.images.studios.coloured" version="0.0.19" />
        <import addon="resource.images.weathericons.white" version="0.0.1" />
        <import addon="resource.images.moviegenreicons.transparent" version="0.0.6" />
        <import addon="resource.images.moviecountryicons.maps" version="0.0.1" />
        <import addon="resource.images.arctic.waves" version="0.0.1" optional="true" />
    </requires>
    <extension debugging="false" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="1" point="xbmc.gui.skin">
        <res aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" height="1080" width="1920" />
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Minimal. Simple.</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Mínimo. Simple.</summary>
        <description lang="en">Arctic Horizon is a minimalistic skin with an emphasis on simplicity.</description>
        <description lang="es">Arctic Horizon es un skin minimalista con énfasis en la simplicidad.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>Creative Commons Attribution Non-Commercial Share-Alike 4.0</license>
        <forum />
        <source />
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
</addons>
